http://www.aialosangeles.org/privacy-policy

ABOUT
What We DoBoardStaffMember DirectoryThanking These SponsorsSponsorship OpportunitiesAIA|LA Strategic PlanResourcesContact
AWARDS
Design Awards & Presidential HonoreesResidential Architecture AwardsRestaurant Design AwardsArchitectural Photography Awards
EVENTS
CalendarTours2°C | Climate Change2X8 | Student ExhibitDesign For Dignity | HousingENCOMPASS: INCLUSIVE ARCHITECTUREPowerful | EquityPurposeful | HealthcareArchitecture Month
ADVOCACY
City Leaders Breakfast SeriesRoundtables + ForumsUrban Design Review SessionsAIA|LA Speakers Bureau
Speakers Bureau Sign-Up
COMMITTEES
2×8 CommitteeArchitecture in HealthcareBuilding Performance & RegulationsCommittee on the EnvironmentDesign Awards CommitteeEmerging ProfessionalsFellows Nominating & MentoringJEDIHistoric Resources CommitteeInterior Architecture CommitteePolitical Outreach CommitteePractice CommitteeUrban Design CommitteeWomen in Architecture Committee
CAREER TOOLS
Job ListingsSubmit a JobView ResumesPost Your ResumeRFP + RFQ OpportuntiesResources for StudentsResources for FirmsContinuing EducationARE ResourcesMentorshipFAIA ProcessContract DocumentsYou & Your ArchitectNational Architect Finder
NEWS
News and BlogsAIALA VideosPress ReleasesNewsroom ExpertsAIA|LA In the MediaAdvertise with AIA|LANewsletter Sign-UpMember NewsCOVID-19-Resources
+ JOIN
AIA|LA WEBSITE
PRIVACY POLICY
AIA Los Angeles Website Privacy Policy
The goal of aialosangeles.org is to provide information and online tools to our members and the public. To do this effectively, certain user data may be collected and/or reviewed.
User-supplied information: Current and future services on aialosangeles.org may require that you give us your name, email address, or other personal information. By providing this information, you can and will be able to transact business via the Internet.
Security
We have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under our control.
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. We may collect personally identifiable information when you visit our site. We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page(s) you visited. We will not sell your personally identifiable information to anyone.
CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY
Your payment and personal information is always safe. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot
be read over the internet.
CANCELLATION/REFUND POLICY & DISCLAIMERS
Cancellations made at least one week prior to the program will be refunded in full, less a $10 cancellation and processing fee. No refunds for cancellations will be given after that time. No refunds shall be issued for no-shows. Registration may be transferred to another individual. AIA|LA reserves the right to cancel any program where the minimum number of pre-registration registrants is not met. If such a cancellation occurs, registrants will be notified and given the opportunity to select an alternate and comparable program to attend. In the event such an alternate and comparable program is not available, then the registration fees will be refunded as appropriate. Furthermore, dates, times, classes, program subject matter, instructors, panelists and fees are subject to change, without notice, at any time at the sole and absolute discretion of AIA|LA.
CONTACT
AIA LOS ANGELES
3780 WILSHIRE BOULEVARD
SUITE 701
LOS ANGELES, CA 90010
T 213 639 0777
INFO@AIALOSANGELES.ORG
SUPPORT
> JOIN AS AIA | ASSOC.
> RENEW AS AIA | ASSOC.
